Woke up in a pixel world
픽셀 세상에서 잠을 깼어
Everything is squares and light
모든 게 네모와 빛뿐이야
Found a heart upon the ground
땅에서 하트 하나를 찾았어
Picked it up it felt so right
집어 들었더니 너무 좋았어
Loading loading love dot exe
로딩 로딩 러브.exe
Ready player two press start
레디 플레이어 투, 시작 버튼 눌러
Pixel love is all I need
픽셀 사랑이면 충분해
Eight bit hearts on every screen
모든 화면에 팔 비트 하트가
Jump and dash and never stop
점프하고 대시하며 절대 멈추지 않아
Level up until we reach the top
정상에 오를 때까지 레벨업
Side by side we fight the boss
나란히 보스와 싸워
Power ups along the way
가는 길에 파워업
Every coin I ever found
내가 찾았던 모든 코인이
Led me closer to today
오늘로 더 가까이 이끌었어
Loading loading love dot exe
로딩 로딩 러브.exe
Ready player two press start
레디 플레이어 투, 시작 버튼 눌러
Pixel love is all I need
픽셀 사랑이면 충분해
Eight bit hearts on every screen
모든 화면에 팔 비트 하트가
Jump and dash and never stop
점프하고 대시하며 절대 멈추지 않아
Level up until we reach the top
정상에 오를 때까지 레벨업
Pixel love is all I need
픽셀 사랑이면 충분해
Eight bit hearts on every screen
모든 화면에 팔 비트 하트가
Jump and dash and never stop
점프하고 대시하며 절대 멈추지 않아
Level up until we reach the top
정상에 오를 때까지 레벨업